HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/003 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- D.O. Misc. -- Sky Chef Grievances Concession Air Griev. -- 24B Master (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chef's Grievances Detroit, MIC Airport Unit, 1987-1988; 14 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chef's Grievances New Orleans, LA Airport Unit, 1986; 15 (Reel 26)
  - Sky Chef's Grievance Omaha, NE Airport Unit, 1988; 16 (Reel 26)
  - Concession Air Grievance Albuquerque, NM Airport Unit, 1988; 17 (Reel 26)
- D.O. Misc. -- Sky Chef Grievances Concession Air Grievances - 25B Master (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chef's Grievances JFK and LaGuardia Airport Units, 1986-1988; 1 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Syracuse, NY Airport Unit, 1987; 2 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Cincinnati, OH Airport Unit, 1986-1987; 3 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chef Grievances Oklahoma, OK Airport Unit, 1986-1987; 4 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chef's Grievances Tulsa, OK Airport Unit, 1986-1988; 5 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chef Grievances Portland, OR Airport Unit, 1986-1988; 6 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Nashville, TN, 1987-1988; 7 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Dallas/Fort Worth, 1986; 8 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Dallas/Fort Worth, 1987-1988; 9 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chef's Grievances San Antonio, TX, 1985; 10 (Reel 27)
  - Sky Chefs Grievances Milwaukee, WI, 1986-1988; 11 (Reel 27)
  - Concession Air Grievances Phoenix, AZ, 1987-1988; 12 (Reel 27)
  - Concession Air Grievances Tucson, AZ, 1987-1988; 13 (Reel 27)
- D.O. Misc. -- Concession Air Grievances. - 26B Master (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Denver, CO, 1987-1988; 1 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Ft. Lauderdale, FL, 1986; 2 (Reel 28)
  - Morty Miller's Notes Re: Grievance #85-50, 3 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Moline, IL, 1988; 4 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances New Orleans, LA, 1986-1988; 5 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances JFK, 1988; 6 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Cincinnati, OH, 1988; 7 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Oklahoma City, OK, 1987; 8 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Allentown, PA and Portland, OR, 1988; 9 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Nashville, TN, 1987-1988; 10 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Dallas/Fort Worth, 1988; 11 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Spokane, WA, 1988; 12 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Madison, WI, 1988; 13 (Reel 28)
  - Concession Air Grievances Milwaukee, WI, 1988; 14 (Reel 28)
- Organization Dept. - Misc. Files (see pages 1&2) -- cartridge no. 1B (Reel 29)
  - A.I. Labor Letters, 1 (Reel 29)
  - Actors Equity Associations, 2 (Reel 29)
  - Affiliated National Hotels, 3 (Reel 29)
  - Agency Shop, 4 (Reel 29)
  - Air Transportation, 5 (Reel 29)
  - Amalgamated Civil Servants, 6 (Reel 29)
  - Am. Culinary Federation, 7 (Reel 29)
  - Am. News Company, 8 (Reel 29)
  - Anti-Trust File, 9 (Reel 29)
  - Associated Hosts, Inc., 10 (Reel 29)
  - Association File, 11 (Reel 29)
  - Automatic Retailers of Am., 12 (Reel 29)
    Scope and Contents
    (ARA) Slater System
  - Brown, B.F., 13 (Reel 29)
  - Blaikie, Miller and Hines, Inc., 14 (Reel 29)
  - Brass Rail, 15 (Reel 29)
  - British Columbia Hotel Association, 16 (Reel 29)
  - Brown Derby Restaurant and Inns, 17 (Reel 29)
  - Canteen Co., 18 (Reel 29)
  - Canus Services Ltd., 19 (Reel 29)
  - Civil Rights Act - Title VII, 20 (Reel 29)
  - Client Newsletter, 21 (Reel 29)
  - Coast Guard Academy, 22 (Reel 29)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 23 (Reel 29)
  - Denny's Restaurant Chain, 24 (Reel 29)
  - Downtowner Motels, 25 (Reel 29)
  - Dual Unions, 26 (Reel 29)
  - EEOC, 27 (Reel 29)
  - Equal Pay, 28 (Reel 29)
  - Executive Order 10988, 29 (Reel 29)
  - Federal Service Contracts Act, 30 (Reel 29)
  - Flaming Pit Restaurant, 31 (Reel 29)
  - GHDI, 32 (Reel 29)
  - Gladieux Corporation, 33 (Reel 29)
  - Peery B. Greever and Co., 34 (Reel 29)
  - Greyhound Post Houses, 35 (Reel 29)
  - Gund, E.J. & Associates, 36 (Reel 29)
  - Hagerty Catering Company, 37 (Reel 29)
  - Hilton Inn - El Paso, TX, 1963; 38 (Reel 29)
    AFL-CIO Convention
  - Hilton Hotels, 1958-1972; 39 (Reel 29)
  - Hotel Association, American, 40 (Reel 29)
  - Holiday Inn Motels, 41 (Reel 29)
  - Horn & Hardart, 42 (Reel 29)
  - Hospital File, 43 (Reel 29)
  - Hot Shoppees, Inc., 44 (Reel 29)
  - Hotel Corporation of America, 45 (Reel 29)
  - Hyatt Corporation, 46 (Reel 29)
  - Hotel, Restaurant, and Inst'al Ed., 47 (Reel 29)
  - Imperial 400 Motel Chain, 48 (Reel 29)
  - Institutions 400, 49 (Reel 29)
  - Interstate Hosts, 50 (Reel 29)
  - Interstate United Corporation, 51 (Reel 29)
  - Host International, 52 (Reel 29)
  - Improved Authorization Card, 53 (Reel 29)
  - Japan Airlines, 54 (Reel 29)
  - Johnson Howard, 55 (Reel 29)
  - Kahler Corporation, 56 (Reel 29)
  - Kries, Milton F., 57 (Reel 29)
  - Labor Client Newsletter, 58 (Reel 29)
  - Labor Law Notes, 59 (Reel 29)
  - Landrum Griffin - Opinions, 60 (Reel 29)
  - Linton's Restaurant, 61 (Reel 29)
  - MacAloon and Associates, Lloyd, 62 (Reel 29)
  - Manger Hotels, 63 (Reel 29)
  - Manley, Inc., 64 (Reel 29)
  - McDonald's Hamburgers, 65 (Reel 29)
  - Marriott In-Flite Services, 66 (Reel 29)
  - Merging AFL-CIO Unions, 67 (Reel 29)
  - Michigan State University, 68 (Reel 29)
  - Michigan Labor Board, 69 (Reel 29)
  - Milner Hotels, 70 (Reel 29)
  - Minimum Wage File, 71 (Reel 29)
  - National Brotherhood of Bartenders, 72 (Reel 29)
  - National Foodservice Mtg., 73 (Reel 29)
  - Nilon Brothers, 74 (Reel 29)
  - Nursing Homes, 75 (Reel 29)
  - National Restaurant Association, 76 (Reel 29)
  - Picketts, 77 (Reel 29)
  - Pick Hotels, 78 (Reel 29)
  - Plant Cafeterias, 79 (Reel 29)
  - Radisson Hotels, 80 (Reel 29)
  - Ramada Inns, 81 (Reel 29)
  - Recruitment and Training, 82 (Reel 29)
  - Restaurant Associates, Inc., 83 (Reel 29)
  - Right to Work, 84 (Reel 29)
  - Rock Resorts Inc., 85 (Reel 29)
  - Royal Inns of America, 86 (Reel 29)
  - Schrafft's, 87 (Reel 29)
  - Service Contracts Act XX, 88 (Reel 29)
  - Stouffers, 89 (Reel 29)
  - Stouffers Campaign, 90 (Reel 29)
  - Schraffts, 91 (Reel 29)
  - C.T. Anderson Legislation Representative, 92 (Reel 29)
  - C.T. Anderson Correspondence, 1961-1965; 93 (Reel 29)
  - C.T. Anderson - House of Representatives, 94 (Reel 29)
    Restaurants and Cafeterias
  - C.T. Anderson and Kenneth Peterson's Expense Ledgers, 95 (Reel 29)
  - G.E.B. Meeting Minutes - Reference to Anderson and Peterson, 96 (Reel 29)
- Organization Dept. Misc. Files (see page 3) - Cartridge 2B (Reel 30)
  - Muer, C.A. Corporation, 1 (Reel 30)
  - National Foundations of H.W. & P. Plans, 2 (Reel 30)
  - National Foundations of H.W. & P. Plans, 3 (Reel 30)
    Seminars
  - National Foundation of H.W. & P. Plans, 4 (Reel 30)
    Resignations
  - National Foundation of H.W. & P. Plans, 5 (Reel 30)
    Myra Wolfgang
  - National Foods Co., 6 (Reel 30)
  - National Foodservice Education and Training Coordinating Council, 7 (Reel 30)
  - Non-Appropriated Fund Activities Government Employees, 8 (Reel 30)
  - Purdue University Apprenticeship Study, 9 (Reel 30)
  - Service Systems Corporation, 10 (Reel 30)
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 11 (Reel 30)
    Smuggler's Inns
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 12 (Reel 30)
    Social Security Tip Bill HR 781
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 13 (Reel 30)
    Sperry Gyroscope - Long Island
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 14 (Reel 30)
    Sportservice
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 15 (Reel 30)
    Springer, G.E. Managing Co.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 16 (Reel 30)
    Steak and Ale
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 17 (Reel 30)
    St. Jude Hospital Fund
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 18 (Reel 30)
    Stouffers
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 19 (Reel 30)
    Strike Benefits AFL-CIO
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 20 (Reel 30)
    Studio Contract Rep.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 21 (Reel 30)
    Szabo Food Service
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 22 (Reel 30)
    Tax Free Meals
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 23 (Reel 30)
    Tips
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 24 (Reel 30)
    Topsy International, Inc.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 25 (Reel 30)
    Travel Expense Act of 1975
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 26 (Reel 30)
    Travelodge Corporation
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 27 (Reel 30)
    Treadway Inn
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 28 (Reel 30)
    Truck Terminal Motels of American
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 29 (Reel 30)
    United States Hotel Corp.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 30 (Reel 30)
    US Department of Labor - Apprenticeship and Training
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 31 (Reel 30)
    Universal Services, Inc.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 32 (Reel 30)
    Valles
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 33 (Reel 30)
    Van de Kamps
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 34 (Reel 30)
    Veterans Canteen Service
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 35 (Reel 30)
    Victoria Stations
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 36 (Reel 30)
    West Coast Food Services Inc.
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 37 (Reel 30)
    Whitehall Hotel - Houston, TX
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 38 (Reel 30)
    White Coffee Pot Restaurants
  - Sheraton Corporation, 1956-1994; 39 (Reel 30)
    Yale University
  - AFL Jurisdiction, 1919-1952; 40 (Reel 30)
- Organization Dept. Misc. Files (see page 4) Cartridge no. 3B (Reel 31)
  - BSEIU, 1 (Reel 31)
  - RCIA - 1688 Brooklyn, NY, 2 (Reel 31)
  - Vending Machines - Teamsters, 3 (Reel 31)
  - Seafarer's Dispute, 4 (Reel 31)
  - Chicago Burlington - Quincy Railroad, 5 (Reel 31)
  - RWDSU - 906, 6 (Reel 31)
  - Internal Disputes File - Canada, 7 (Reel 31)
  - AFL Jurisdiction Awards to IU, 8 (Reel 31)
  - Article XX Cases, 9 (Reel 31)
    RWDSU v. #257
  - Article XX Cases, 10 (Reel 31)
    #58 v. RWDSU
  - Article XX Cases, 11 (Reel 31)
    SEIU v. #57
  - Article XX Cases, 12 (Reel 31)
    Pago Pago
  - Article XX Cases, 13 (Reel 31)
    SEIU v. 283
  - Article XX Cases, 14 (Reel 31)
    #58 v. In.Bell
  - Article XX Case, 15 (Reel 31)
    SEIU v. #593
  - Article XX Cases, 16 (Reel 31)
    Amtrak
  - Article XX Cases, 17 (Reel 31)
    #131 v. AFSCME
  - Article XX Cases, 18 (Reel 31)
    #222 v. IUEW
  - Articles XX Cases, 19 (Reel 31)
    BSEIU v. #440
  - Article XX Cases, 20 (Reel 31)
    OPEIU v. #508
  - Article XX Cases, 21 (Reel 31)
  - Article XX Cases, 22 (Reel 31)
    #11 v. RCIA
  - Article XX Cases, 23 (Reel 31)
    #505 v. RWDSU
  - NLRB, 24 (Reel 31)
    Election Reports
  - NLRB, 25 (Reel 31)
    Certification Petitions
  - NLRB, 26 (Reel 31)
  - NLRB, 27 (Reel 31)
    Correspondence
  - NLRB, 28 (Reel 31)
    Organizers Meetings
  - NLRB, 29 (Reel 31)
    Union Shop Clause
  - NLRB, 30 (Reel 31)
    Rulings
  - NLRB, 31 (Reel 31)
    Agency Shop
  - Organizing File, 32 (Reel 31)
  - Organizing Report - 1971 Convention, 33 (Reel 31)
  - Membership Count, 34 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Brookdale Ice Cream Co., 35 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Canus Prebuilt, Ltd., 36 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Food Giant Markets, Inc., 37 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Green Enterprises, 38 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Huylers, 39 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Lakewood Foods, Inc., 40 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Manley, Inc., 41 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Marriot, 42 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Shine Hotels, 43 (Reel 31)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Topsy's International, 44 (Reel 31)
- Organization Dept. Misc. Files (see pages 5&6) - Cartridge no. 4B (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Dutch Inns of America, 1 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 2 (Reel 32)
    Frank Fries
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 3 (Reel 32)
    Philadelphia
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 4 (Reel 32)
    Mt. Vernon, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 5 (Reel 32)
    Miami Beach, FL
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 6 (Reel 32)
    Albany, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 7 (Reel 32)
    Hempstead, LI
  - Contracts and Agreements - Steak and Brew, 8 (Reel 32)
    Boston, MA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Campco Pacific Inc., 9 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Bourbon Orleans Limited, 10 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Copper Wheel Restaurant, 11 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - B/G Foods, Inc., 12 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - International House of Pancakes, 13 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Gladieux Food Services, Inc., 14 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 15 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 16 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 17 (Reel 32)
    Atlanta, GA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 18 (Reel 32)
    Baltimore, MD
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 19 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 20 (Reel 32)
    Buffalo, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 21 (Reel 32)
    New York, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 22 (Reel 32)
    Cleveland, OH
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 23 (Reel 32)
    Ft. Lauderdale, FL
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 24 (Reel 32)
    Bal Harbor and Miami, FL
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 25 (Reel 32)
    Hempstead, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 26 (Reel 32)
    McKeesport, PA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 27 (Reel 32)
    Philadelphia, PA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 28 (Reel 32)
    Newark, DE
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 29 (Reel 32)
    Providence, RI
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 30 (Reel 32)
    Troy, MI
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 31 (Reel 32)
    Winchester, VA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 32 (Reel 32)
    St. Louis, MO
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 33 (Reel 32)
    Los Angeles, CA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Schraffts, 34 (Reel 32)
    San Francisco, CA
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 35 (Reel 32)
    New York Coliseum
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 36 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 37 (Reel 32)
    Birmingham, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 38 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 39 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 40 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 41 (Reel 32)
    Brooklyn, NY
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 42 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 43 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Harry M. Stevens, Inc., 44 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 45 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 46 (Reel 32)
    Agreements
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 47 (Reel 32)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 1974; 48 (Reel 32)
    Negotiations
- Organization Dept. Misc. Files (see page 6) - Cartridge no. 5B (Reel 33)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 1 (Reel 33)
    Negotiations (cont.)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 1971-1978; 2 (Reel 33)
    NY Playboy Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 1968-1970; 3 (Reel 33)
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 1964-1967; 4 (Reel 33)
    New York Playboy Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 5 (Reel 33)
    San Francisco Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 6 (Reel 33)
    St. Louis Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 7 (Reel 33)
    Miami Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 8 (Reel 33)
    Los Angeles Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 9 (Reel 33)
    Kansas City Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 10 (Reel 33)
    Great Gorge, NJ
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 11 (Reel 33)
    Detroit Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 12 (Reel 33)
    Cincinnati Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 13 (Reel 33)
    Chicago Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 14 (Reel 33)
    Boston Club
  - Contracts and Agreements - Playboy Clubs International, 15 (Reel 33)
    Atlanta Club
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Agriesti, Jo-Marie-Gallo, Vincent P. - Roll 86 Master (Reel 34)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Agriesti, Jo Marie - Gallo, Vincent P., 1989-1990; 1 (Reel 34)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Galvez, Hector-Papageorge, George -- Roll 87 Master (Reel 35)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Galvez, Hector - Papageorge, George, 1989-1990; 1 (Reel 35)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Pascual, Manuel-Tamann, Henry -- Roll 88 Master (Reel 36)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Pascual, Manuel - Tamann, Henry, 1989-1990 (Reel 36)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Taylor, Donald-Carr, Andy -- Roll 89 Master (Reel 37)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Taylor, Donald - Carr, Andy, 1989-1990 (Reel 37)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Castro, Gloria-Granfield, Bill - Roll 90 Master (Reel 38)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Castro, Gloria - Granfield, Bill, 1989-1990 (Reel 38)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Guthman, Gary-Picard, Paul -- Roll 91 Master (Reel 39)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Guthman, Gary - Picard, Paul, 1989-1990 (Reel 39)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Pitta, Vito-Strieb, L. - Roll 92 Master (Reel 40)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Pitta, Vito - Strieb, L., 1989-1990 (Reel 40)
- 1989 & 90 Organizer Wkly Report Forms -- Sullivan, F.-Zenich, T. -- Roll 93 Master (Reel 41)
  - Organizer Weekly Report Forms: Sullivan, F. - Zenich, T., 1989-1990 (Reel 41)
- L.S.O. 1977-1980 -- Local #10 1980 -- Local #116 1977 - cartridge no. 1-A (Reel 42)
  - Local #10 Documents 2-20, 1980; 1 (Reel 42)
  - Local #12, 1977; 2 (Reel 42)
  - Local #12, 1978; 3 (Reel 42)
  - Local #12, 1979; 4 (Reel 42)
  - Local #12, 1980; 5 (Reel 42)
  - Local #21, 1977; 6 (Reel 42)
  - Local #23, 1977; 7 (Reel 42)
  - Local #25, 1977; 8 (Reel 42)
  - Local #25, 1978; 9 (Reel 42)
  - Local #25, 1979; 10 (Reel 42)
  - Local #25, 1980; 11 (Reel 42)
  - Local #54, 1978; 12 (Reel 42)
  - Local #54, 1979; 13 (Reel 42)
  - Local #54, 1980; 14 (Reel 42)
  - Local #58, 1979; 15 (Reel 42)
  - Local #58, 1980; 16 (Reel 42)
  - Local #60, 1978; 17 (Reel 42)
  - Local #60, 1979; 18 (Reel 42)
  - Local #64, 1977; 19 (Reel 42)
  - Local #64, 1978; 20 (Reel 42)
  - Local #64, 1979; 21 (Reel 42)
  - Local #105, 1978; 22 (Reel 42)
  - Local #116, 1977; 23 (Reel 42)
- L.S.O. 1977-1980 - Local #116-1978 - Local #634-1979 - cartridge no. 2-A (Reel 43)
  - Local #116, 1978; 1 (Reel 43)
  - Local #117, 1978; 2 (Reel 43)
  - Local #117, 1979; 3 (Reel 43)
  - Local #118, 1980; 4 (Reel 43)
  - Local #122, 1977; 5 (Reel 43)
  - Local #122, 1978; 6 (Reel 43)
  - Local #166, 1980; 7 (Reel 43)
  - Local #208, 1977; 8 (Reel 43)
  - Local #208, 1980; 9 (Reel 43)
  - Local #222, 1978; 10 (Reel 43)
  - Local #235, 1977; 11 (Reel 43)
  - Local #235, 1978; 12 (Reel 43)
  - Local #235, 1979; 13 (Reel 43)
  - Local #251, 1979; 14 (Reel 43)
  - Local #261, 1979; 15 (Reel 43)
  - Local #264, 1980; 16 (Reel 43)
  - Local #270, 1977; 17 (Reel 43)
  - Local #274, 1978; 18 (Reel 43)
  - Local #280, 1978; 19 (Reel 43)
  - Local #294, 1979; 20 (Reel 43)
  - Local #294, 1980; 21 (Reel 43)
  - Local #298, 1977; 22 (Reel 43)
  - Local #310, 1977; 23 (Reel 43)
  - Local #310, 1978; 24 (Reel 43)
  - Local #450, 1980; 25 (Reel 43)
  - Local #471, 1976; 26 (Reel 43)
  - Local #471, 1977; 27 (Reel 43)
  - Local #471, 1978; 28 (Reel 43)
  - Local #471, 1980; 29 (Reel 43)
  - Local #505, 1976; 30 (Reel 43)
  - Local #505, 1977; 31 (Reel 43)
  - Local #505, 1977; 32 (Reel 43)
  - Local #505, 1979; 33 (Reel 43)
  - Local #505, 1980; 34 (Reel 43)
  - Local #527, 1977; 35 (Reel 43)
  - Local #573, 1976; 36 (Reel 43)
  - Local #573, 1977; 37 (Reel 43)
  - Local #634, 1977; 38 (Reel 43)
  - Local #634, 1978; 39 (Reel 43)
  - Local #634, 1979; 40 (Reel 43)
- Organizer Files - Int'l LSO Files - W.R.O. Org. Files Cartridge no. 3-A (Reel 44)
  - Local #634, 1980; 1 (Reel 44)
  - Local #688, 1978; 2 (Reel 44)
  - Local #703, 1978; 3 (Reel 44)
  - Local #703, 1979; 4 (Reel 44)
  - Local #703, 1980; 5 (Reel 44)
  - Local #743, 1980; 6 (Reel 44)
  - Local #757, 1979; 7 (Reel 44)
  - Local #868, 1977; 8 (Reel 44)
  - Local #868, 1980; 9 (Reel 44)
  - Local #886, 1976; 10 (Reel 44)
  - Local #886, 1977; 11 (Reel 44)
  - Local #886, 1978; 12 (Reel 44)
  - Local #886, 1979; 13 (Reel 44)
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 14 (Reel 44)
    Belardi, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 15 (Reel 44)
    Bramlet, A.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 16 (Reel 44)
    DeLeon, L.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 17 (Reel 44)
    Dempsey, H.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 18 (Reel 44)
    Felix, F.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 19 (Reel 44)
    Gamberg, R.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 20 (Reel 44)
    Gaw, R.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 21 (Reel 44)
    Giesick, R.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 22 (Reel 44)
    Guise, B.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 23 (Reel 44)
    Hansen, T.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 24 (Reel 44)
    Kleifgen, B.
- W.R.O. Org. Files Cartridge No. 4-A (Reel 45)
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 1 (Reel 45)
    McClellan, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 2 (Reel 45)
    McDonough, C.T.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 3 (Reel 45)
    McHugh, G.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 4 (Reel 45)
    McLaughlin, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 5 (Reel 45)
    Marolda, F.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 6 (Reel 45)
    Marolda, R.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 7 (Reel 45)
    Medeiros, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files`, 1974-1980; 8 (Reel 45)
    Meister, P.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 9 (Reel 45)
    Mureo, G.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 10 (Reel 45)
    Perkins, C.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 11 (Reel 45)
    Paulsen, K.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 12 (Reel 45)
    Peterson, T.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 13 (Reel 45)
    Rabe, C.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 14 (Reel 45)
    Riley, L.
- W.R.O. Org. Files Cartridge no. 5-A (Reel 46)
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 1 (Reel 46)
    Richardson, M.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 2 (Reel 46)
    Rutledge, An.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 3 (Reel 46)
    Rutledge, Ar.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 4 (Reel 46)
    Salerno, M.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 5 (Reel 46)
    Schoutey, B.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 6 (Reel 46)
    Scimeca, A.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 7 (Reel 46)
    Scimeca, T.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 8 (Reel 46)
    Small, T.A.